filmaffinity.com 2016-11-29

# Filmaffinity Privacy Policy - FilmAffinity

* At Filmaffinity, we care about your privacy. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy:

* Filmaffinity is a website created by Pablo Kurt Verdú and Daniel Nicolás. It is part of the company Filmaffinity S.L. We remain deeply commited to maintaining the privacy of our users by unswervingly abiding by current legal regulations.

* Filmaffinity guarantees that all the information gathered online will be stored in an electronically protected database. We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect online.

* Under no circumstances will this information be shared with a third party.

* The data holder has the right to access all data files at all times and has the right to modify or cancel registration, complying with all the requirements laid down in current regulations on the subject of personal data protection. Users may at any given point revoke their given consent on the handling of their personal data.

* The Filmaffinity database is legally registered under the Spanish Data Protection Agency. 

* Filmaffinity does not sell, rent or make available to third parties the personal data provided by users.

* Like most websites and search engines, Filmaffinity uses cookies in order to provide a better user experience and to serve relevant ads.

* In order to access all Filmaffinity services, you need to register. When you register with us, you will be required to provide certain information. Whilst we publicly use information regarding your country and movie ratings in order to offer our Movie Soulmate services, your name, email address and birthday will remain completely private. Your Movie Soulmates, however, will be able to access your username and city and country of residence, as well as your personal movie ratings. 

* Filmaffinity also reserves the right to send emails to registered users regarding changes, updates, and other related events. 

* The Filmaffinity database is registered under and follows the regulations of the Spanish Data Protection Agency, ruled under European Union Laws.

* Filmaffinity is in no way liable for the content and opinions found on the pages of its members and it reserves the right to partially or completely delete any comment or input that may not abide by our community standards. Similarly, Filmaffinity does not guarantee the publication of received ratings and reviews, and it reserves the right to alter, edit or delete them without prior notification. Furthermore, Filmaffinity reserves the right to delete any user content that is deemed inappropriate or disrespectful. The latter particularly applies to offensive reviews, as well as ratings which may be under suspicion for tampering with average ratings. 

* See more on our 'Terms and Conditions' section.

* Terms and conditions 

Filmaffinity reserves the right to edit or delete any user data that may be considered inappropriate or obsolete without previous notification. Any indice of inappropriate use of the website, or tampering thereof will result in the subsequent deletion of suspicious accounts. 

In order to ensure the reliability, transparency, impartiality and objectivity of the data available on our website, Filmaffinity reserves the right to delete any ratings belonging to newly registered users having less than 6 months’ activity on the website, less than 10 logins, or less than 200 rated films. Special attention will be paid to new film releases in each country, as well as recently awarded movies, current nominees, or new films with few ratings that are thus susceptible of tampering. 

Additionally, Filmaffinity remains committed to improving existing automatic controls, such as filters, automatic and manually controlled corrective measures, as well as tampering detection systems for movie ratings. 

At Filmaffinity, we would like to underline and stress our commitment to reliability, transparency, impartiality, and objectivity regarding all information currently stored in the Filmaffinity database. Our commitment strikes us as particularly important in the following areas: 

Average ratings on all movie and TV series. User movie ratings. Selected excerpts and reviews from relevant media. Trending media & professional reviews. 

* In order to enhance your experience with our site, many of our web pages use cookies. Cookies are text files we place in your computer's browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering at one of our sites. However, once you choose to furnish the site with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie. We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our sites. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our web pages (e.g. to recognize you by name when you return to our site) or save your password in password-protected areas. We also may use cookies to offer you products, programs, or services.
